‎SPOOKY IN LOVE
‎I got you, Cheon Yeo-ri.
‎EPISODE 8
‎I'm sorry.
‎I was in court and missed your call.
‎I sent the police to the atelier
‎once I saw your text.
‎Okay.
‎So there's another body in this building?
‎Split up. Get to it.
‎This way.
‎In here!
‎How did she know there was a body here?
‎Was this how she found Jang Eun-ju's body?
‎I told you I'm Si-o,
‎so that makes me him!
‎Let go of me!
‎Come on.
‎You must've been startled.
‎Cheon Yeo-ri, you really…
‎What is going on?
‎Should I actually
‎let off a bomb this time?
‎My Ha-ri filmed this herself.
‎Isn't it so weird and unsettling?
‎If it were anyone else, seeing ghosts
‎wouldn't be such a problem.
‎But for someone who could become
‎the chairperson of Reina Group
‎to be going around
‎doing such bizarre things…
‎Isn't that unacceptable?
‎The company is at a critical juncture,
‎and she's only creating
‎trouble for herself.
‎Even her failed engagement six years ago
‎sent the stock price tumbling.
‎Speaking of which,
‎we'd like to call an extraordinary
‎shareholders' meeting soon.
‎We were hoping that you, Director Gong,
‎along with the other elders
‎who were loyal to the late chairman,
‎would throw your support behind us.
‎If we hold an extraordinary
‎shareholders' meeting,
‎the agenda would be…
‎A motion for the removal
‎of Reina's CEO, of course.
‎What is it you wanted to say?
‎You said you wanted to wait for Yeo-ri.
‎It's about the rumors
‎that have been going around about her.
‎I wanted us to watch this together.
‎Something similar happened
‎with Seung-jae last time.
‎You know Yeo-ri was photographed
‎where Jang Eun-ju's body was found, right?
‎This time, another body was found
‎where Yeo-ri had gone.
‎She identified exactly where it was
‎as if someone had told her
‎where to look.
‎I heard the deceased was Si-o.
‎Wasn't he the art director for Reina?
‎It's true that
‎Si-o is dead.
‎It's also true that his body was there.
‎Don't try to brush this off
‎as another coincidence.
‎Cha Gi-u told me the same thing, Grandma.
‎She only got away
‎because he refused to testify.
‎First, Jang Eun-ju's death
‎and now this incident.
‎When coincidences keep happening,
‎there has to be a reason, right?
‎Grandma, it's clear
‎that Yeo-ri is still haunted.
‎How can someone who lets ghosts
‎guide her to corpses run a company?
‎What happened?
‎The truth is…
‎Mr. Ma had asked for my help.
‎He found out that Si-o was an art director
‎who had worked with us
‎and asked if I could identify him.
‎Mr. Ma meant to accompany me,
‎but he got held up,
‎and I ended up arriving first.
‎Grandma, you know
‎that doesn't make sense.
‎It's obvious she just made up that excuse.
‎Why doesn't it make sense?
‎And you.
‎You tailed me?
‎I know what you're trying to achieve
‎with these stunts,
‎but you can't beat me
‎with tricks like that.
‎Ha-ri.
‎You can leave now.
‎Grandma.
‎I'm disappointed in you too.
‎Whatever the reason,
‎you shouldn't give her any leverage.
‎I'm sorry.
‎The directors of our affiliates,
‎including Gong,
‎will make this an issue
‎like they did six years ago.
‎Here's what we'll do.
‎Mr. Ma.
‎He's had a standard elite career path,
‎and those in legal circles say
‎he's upright and incorruptible.
‎And his looks…
‎aren't too bad either.
‎Let's set a date
‎for the engagement ceremony.
‎Gang-uk.
‎Can we meet tomorrow?
‎You made it.
‎This is Siena Hall?
‎I like the look and atmosphere.
‎My dad gifted it to my mom
‎for their tenth wedding anniversary.
‎I see. It's a really special place then.
‎How did they meet?
‎My dad studied architecture.
‎He traveled to Siena, Italy
‎while studying abroad in Spain,
‎and met my mom there.
‎So he named it after where they first met?
‎Man, that's so romantic.
‎If Director Ok takes over Reina Group,
‎the first thing she'll do
‎is tear this building down.
‎And then she'll turn what's left
‎into an art gallery.
‎Then I'll no longer
‎be able to protect this place.
‎We can't let that happen.
‎I'll fight for Siena too.
‎Were you able to explain
‎the video Ha-ri took that day?
‎Actually, that made things worse for us.
‎My grandma wants us to get engaged
‎as soon as possible,
‎before the rumors spread further.
‎What should we do?
‎It looks like we might actually have to
‎hold an engagement ceremony.
‎That's too much to ask from you, isn't it?
‎It's not.
‎I'd actually prefer it.
‎At first,
‎I was afraid to be around you.
‎And the ghosts too.
‎But you were shouldering
‎everything on your own
‎so you wouldn't burden me
‎or anyone around you.
‎That's not something just anyone can do.
‎It shows how kind
‎and how warm you are as a person.
‎I wish others could see that too.
‎Now,
‎when I think of you,
‎my heart softens and I feel butterflies.
‎The sky seems clearer too.
‎Even standing here with you
‎feels like a gift to me.
‎So if we were to get engaged,
‎I'm all for it.
‎Because my feelings for you…
‎are genuine, Yeo-ri.
‎Because my feelings for you
‎are ‎genuine, ‎Yeo-ri.
‎-We heard from Singapore.
‎-Yes?
‎They want us to confirm attendance
‎by the end of the week.
‎Just tell them
‎we'll be attending for now.
‎Tell them we'll inform them later
‎whether it'll be me or Mr. Bong attending.
‎Yes, ma'am.
‎-You can go.
‎-Oh, right.
‎-Hello.
‎-Hey.
‎What happened? Did you sprain your ankle?
‎Yeah, on the stairs.
‎Hyeong-min, got any pain relief patches?
‎-I'm fine.
‎-No, I don't.
‎Mr. Ma, you know
‎a bit about hand acupuncture.
‎-Hand acupuncture?
‎-Forget it.
‎I do have a license,
‎but how'd you know that?
‎I saw it in your car last time.
‎I keep one in the car just in case.
‎My grandma always worries…
‎Grandma.
‎What's going on? Is she ill?
‎No, it's not that.
‎The Black Monkey…
‎Pil-dong, what should I do?
‎About what?
‎Can you at least tell me what's going on?
‎Did anyone oppose or disapprove
‎when you married your wife?
‎-Totally.
‎-People did disapprove
‎-because of the age gap.
‎-It's ten years.
‎-Hey, it's just seven.
‎-Right, seven years.
‎That means she's a year older than Yeo-ri.
‎-What's her zodiac sign?
‎-Her zodiac sign is a goat.
‎-A goat?
‎-Yeah.
‎Year of the goat, a year older.
‎-Pil-dong.
‎-Yeah?
‎Can you lend me your wife's ‎saju?
‎I swear it'll save my life.
‎I can't save you if you don't tell me
‎exactly what's going on.
‎So the thing is…
‎I need to get engaged soon.
‎Right, you're getting engaged… What?
‎You're getting engaged?
‎-Yeah.
‎-What kind of stupidity is this?
‎-What are you thinking?
‎-Jeez.
‎Use your words.
‎What if she's someone who grew up
‎without a proper upbringing?
‎You're getting engaged,
‎and you didn't even tell me?
‎If you'd told me sooner,
‎I'd have taken a better look at her.
‎Were you trying to sneak out
‎your engagement announcement
‎like a snake slithering over a wall?
‎Huh?
‎Look, it's not like I'd call it off
‎even if you disapproved.
‎What if you asked Yeo-ri weird questions
‎and ended up scaring her off?
‎That's why I had her tell you
‎we were just close friends.
‎Jeez.
‎Come on, Grandma.
‎She's a really good person,
‎and she's pretty.
‎Fine then.
‎Okay. Go ahead.
‎As long as you like her,
‎I won't disapprove.
‎-Really?
‎-However,
‎there's something I need.
‎Need what?
‎What do you mean, "what?"
‎Her ‎saju,‎ of course, and her zodiac.
‎Who cares about that in this day and age?
‎I don't care about anything else.
‎Checking her ‎saju
‎and zodiac is the bare minimum.
‎That's practically everything!
‎Why are you so reluctant?
‎Don't tell me her zodiac sign is…
‎-the Black…
‎-No, nothing's black.
‎Then what?
‎What year was she born?
‎The year of the goat. She's a White Goat.
‎It's a good match.
‎It's very good.
‎-Are you sure?
‎-Yes.
‎It's the best ‎saju
‎for a civil servant's wife.
‎-Is that so?
‎-The husband is surrounded by temptation
‎and could suffer from many mishaps,
‎but the wife's ‎saju‎ is enough
‎to save and protect him through it all.
‎You should push for this marriage.
‎Well, Gang-uk isn't the type
‎to fall for any temptation.
‎But then again,
‎being a prosecutor
‎comes with its share of risks and dangers.
‎Anyway, since you say
‎they're a good match,
‎I feel at ease now.
‎-Go ahead.
‎-Really?
‎You mean she passed?
‎I'll call you back
‎as soon as the date is set.
‎Okay. I love you, Madam Pang.
‎Bye.
‎It's a yes. She approved.
‎Man, I was terrified that she'd catch on.
‎Wait, what about the one-year age gap
‎between my wife and Ms. Cheon?
‎My grandma has no reason to check her ID.
‎I'm sure she'll take my word for it.
‎How did you even think
‎to use his wife's ‎saju?
‎Madam Pang is too quick-witted
‎for her own good.
‎I knew it'd be safer to give her
‎an existing ‎saju‎ than something made up.
‎Yes, that's true.
‎Before we got married,
‎my mom asked someone about my wife's ‎saju.
‎-Okay.
‎-Turns out,
‎my wife's ‎saju‎ is the perfect fit
‎for a civil servant's wife.
‎Gang-uk and I have a lot in common,
‎so I guess that's why
‎we got similar fortune-telling results.
‎What do you and Mr. Ma have in common?
‎I find it very frustrating
‎that I even need to spell it out for you.
‎Look.
‎-We're both civil servants.
‎-Okay.
‎-Ma is smart and capable.
‎-That's right.
‎-I'm capable too.
‎-Sure.
‎Ma has good looks.
‎-Forget it. What kind of reaction is that?
‎-I didn't say anything.
‎Aside from the age gap
‎that my wife and I have,
‎I can't think of a single thing
‎Gang-uk and I don't have in common.
‎-You're right.
‎-Of course.
‎-You're extra eloquent today.
‎-It's nothing.
‎So are all hurdles cleared now, Mr. Ma?
‎No more obstacles?
‎That's right. None left.
‎I think?
‎-A formal family meeting?
‎-Yeah.
‎I can't meet my in-laws for the first time
‎at the engagement ceremony.
‎His grandmother is his only family left,
‎so we should meet her.
‎I'm sorry things keep snowballing
‎because of me.
‎No, don't be sorry.
‎My grandmother mentioned
‎a formal family meeting too.
‎So I'll bring her to Reina Hotel
‎next Wednesday then?
‎Yes.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎Since we've decided to take the plunge,
‎why don't we make the best of it?
‎"We"?
‎See you on Wednesday then.
‎Okay.
‎-The lady in the white dress?
‎-Yeah!
‎She was so--
‎-Hello.
‎You can get in.
‎-Pardon?
‎-Okay.
‎Thank you.
‎-Goodbye.
‎Take care.
‎She's not at all like the rumors.
‎Right?
‎-She's even prettier up close.
‎-Yeah, totally.
‎No way. Matching rings?
‎It's an engagement ring.
‎He gave it to me yesterday.
‎He asked me out to eat,
‎-then suggested we take a walk.
‎-Okay.
‎Then he said we should sit on a bench,
‎so I did without a second thought.
‎Suddenly, he got down on one knee
‎and put the ring on my finger.
‎It must've been nice.
‎-What about you, Ms. Eom?
‎-Me?
‎"What's this?"
‎It was in my ice cream.
‎I almost swallowed my own engagement ring.
‎Why didn't you?
‎I should have.
‎Oh, let's see.
‎Hey.
‎I should've picked you up, Grandma.
‎I'm sorry.
‎I had to wrap up a case urgently.
‎Goodness, don't apologize.
‎Your work should always come first.
‎I arrived safe and sound,
‎so take your time.
‎What? You're already there?
‎Okay. I'll hurry over.
‎You do that.
‎So this is where
‎my granddaughter-in-law works.
‎As you instructed,
‎we decorated the dining room
‎so it looks simple yet classy.
‎I also gave the kitchen
‎special instructions
‎to cater the meal to the elderly.
‎Goodness, I forgot my medication.
‎I'll go get it
‎and bring it to the dining room.
‎Oh, dear.
‎Are you feeling unwell?
‎No, I'm fine.
‎You could end up falling over
‎and hurting yourself.
‎Lean on me.
‎Let's go sit down over there.
‎Come along.
‎Oh, my.
‎Your bones must be heavier than they look.
‎Hello?
‎Oh, really?
‎I'll come downstairs then. Thank you.
‎You look terribly pale.
‎Should I call the paramedics for you?
‎No. I just need to rest for a while.
‎Thank you.
‎MY GANG-UK
‎Hey.
‎Yeah.
‎I'm right inside the entrance,
‎on the couches.
‎Oh, you're bringing your girlfriend?
‎Okay. That's fine.
‎I'll sit right here and wait.
‎Okay.
‎Bye.
‎I'm waiting here to meet
‎my grandson's wife-to-be.
‎What brings you here?
‎I'm here on similar business.
‎To meet your grandson's girlfriend?
‎No, my granddaughter's boyfriend.
‎Goodness, what a coincidence this is.
‎My grandson's girlfriend works here.
‎Really? In which department?
‎I don't know anything about that.
‎I do know that she's lovely.
‎According to her ‎saju,
‎she'll make a perfectly devoted housewife
‎to support and assist
‎her civil servant husband.
‎So I'm welcoming her with open arms.
‎What about you?
‎Do you like
‎your granddaughter's boyfriend?
‎Well, yes.
‎Yes?
‎I'm relieved since he seems willing
‎to support my granddaughter.
‎After all, it's not uncommon for a man
‎to move in with his wife's family now.
‎Oh, he plans to move in with your family?
‎Well, these days,
‎many women have a career.
‎You're very blessed. Congratulations.
‎Yes, thank you. That goes for you too.
‎Yes, it does. Thank you.
‎-Grandma!
‎This is my grandmother, ma'am.
‎Perhaps we were meant to meet
‎the way we did.
‎Perhaps so.
‎I am quite fond of
‎my future granddaughter-in-law.
‎I'm into fortune-telling and reading ‎saju,
‎so I had their compatibility checked.
‎I was told they're a good match
‎as their zodiac signs are a horse and--
‎-Oh, my.
‎-What's wrong?
‎You…
‎Are you all right?
‎Yes. The water went down the wrong pipe.
‎I'm sorry.
‎-Are you okay?
‎-I'm fine.
‎Do you care about fortunes and ‎saju
‎and things of that nature?
‎Things like that?
‎Oh, yes, I do.
‎But not this time.
‎Their marriage has already been decided,
‎and I didn't want to jinx anything.
‎They're not children either,
‎so I decided to respect their decision.
‎I see.
‎As I said, the fortune-teller
‎said they're a good match.
‎There's one thing that bothers me though.
‎You didn't mean
‎what you said earlier, did you?
‎About having your grandson-in-law move in.
‎I'm not sure if you're aware,
‎but Gang-uk attended
‎the most prestigious university in Korea.
‎After he was admitted,
‎he passed the bar exam
‎before he even graduated.
‎What was it called?
‎Coming first in a state exam!
‎No, let's say
‎he passed with flying colors.
‎He was known to have a brilliant mind
‎and passed the bar with flying colors.
‎So to have him move in with your family…
‎-There's no way I'd accept or allow that.
‎-Be quiet, Grandma.
‎You be quiet.
‎-That's what I think.
‎-I see.
‎You mentioned
‎a devoted housewife earlier, right?
‎-Well…
‎-We no longer live in such an era.
‎I'm not sure how to explain this.
‎Although Yeo-ri
‎had to withdraw halfway through
‎due to personal reasons,
‎she attended the top school in the US,
‎Wharton School,
‎to get a global MBA degree.
‎She was smart enough
‎to secure a spot there easily.
‎-She currently manages this hotel,
‎-What's she talking about?
‎-It ranks even higher.
‎-but in the future,
‎she will likely take over
‎and manage Reina Group as a whole.
‎So she desperately needs a husband
‎who can support her.
‎Oh, please. A husband supporting his wife?
‎It's not like Gang-uk
‎is an incapable fool.
‎He's a very busy man.
‎He can't assist your granddaughter.
‎Is that what you think?
‎No, of course I should
‎assist and support Yeo-ri.
‎I should.
‎I also support Gang-uk myself, ma'am.
‎You saw it that day, didn't you?
‎I'll get the gate right away.
‎If it's to help Gang-uk,
‎I can go anywhere and do anything.
‎Isn't that how a wife shows real support?
‎Something is a bit off here.
‎Did you have to talk such nonsense?
‎I had to because she talked about
‎having you move in with her family.
‎I won't let you move in with your in-laws
‎and get stomped all over.
‎Still, you can't say you'll reconsider
‎when it's already been decided.
‎Why did you lie to me?
‎She owns a number of motels…
‎I mean, hotels.
‎She's a rich heiress.
‎I didn't lie to you.
‎I just didn't tell you everything.
‎And why does it matter
‎how many hotels Yeo-ri owns?
‎I made my decision based on her alone.
‎Don't you trust me?
‎You should marry an ordinary girl
‎from an ordinary family.
‎Other than the fact that she's pretty,
‎she's completely ordinary.
‎She doesn't brag about being rich.
‎And let's be honest,
‎you said you only cared
‎about her zodiac sign.
‎It's not fair to pull the plug now.
‎That's right.
‎Come to think of it, Shaman Sim
‎got your fortunes completely wrong.
‎-I should call to yell at him for--
‎-No, Grandma.
‎I want you to like Yeo-ri.
‎That would make me really happy.
‎Please?
‎Why you little…
‎-Do you like her that much?
‎-Yes, so much.
‎Oh, dear.
‎Oh, goodness.
‎Fine.
‎Don't forget that I have your back.
‎Don't you ever let them intimidate you.
‎-Got it?
‎-You bet.
‎I'm your grandson after all. Right?
‎It's all over for good now.
‎Let's drink. Cheers!
‎Did the zodiac thing work?
‎They forgot all about that
‎when they started bragging about us.
‎This is why you shouldn't do bad things.
‎Karma comes back around.
‎What if she finds out?
‎Don't you need a plan or something?
‎Whatever.
‎I'll only worry about
‎what's happening right now.
‎That's right, Mr. Ma.
‎You can worry about that later.
‎Pil-dong, people really disapproved
‎of your marriage, right?
‎-Yeah, a bit.
‎-Right?
‎I bet it was really bad.
‎I wouldn't call it "really bad."
‎Like I said, the age gap was…
‎But you know, people recognize it
‎when a couple is meant to be together.
‎If someone is good enough,
‎they eventually see it.
‎I'm putting up a wall to keep you safe.
‎Every now and then,
‎I want to drink
‎among some ordinary people.
‎Seriously, your wife is so beautiful.
‎Why do you hate going home after work?
‎It boils down to their personality
‎and temperament.
‎Hello?
‎Have you eaten yet, Yeo-ri?
‎No, not yet.
‎What about you?
‎Oh, I'm…
‎You're having dinner.
‎With Investigator Ko and Hyeong-min?
‎Yes.
‎Yeo-ri, I think we've done
‎almost everything together,
‎but we haven't eaten
‎together much, have we?
‎-We haven't?
‎-No.
‎Hyeong-min recommended
‎some popular eateries.
‎He insisted I take you.
‎Are you free tomorrow?
‎I am.
‎So where is this popular eatery?
‎What?
‎Oh, it's…
‎I'll get the details from Hyeong-min
‎and send you the link.
‎And actually…
‎There's something I must do with you
‎before we get engaged.
‎What's that?
‎You'll find out when we meet tomorrow.
‎Okay then. See you tomorrow.
‎Bye.
‎Hey, Hyeong-min.
‎Hyeong-min.
‎-Give me a list of the popular hangouts.
‎-Popular hangouts?
‎-Are we going for a second round?
‎-Cut it out and hurry.
‎Something he needs to do with me
‎before we get engaged?
‎What?
‎Proposing with a ring?
‎No way.
‎The ceremony is coming up.
‎I guess
‎I do need a ring.
‎Man, this doesn't look right.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎This is where the soccer player,
‎Cha Hyeon-u, proposed to his wife.
‎I see.
‎-Here are your desserts.
‎-Thank you.
‎It's an engagement ring.
‎It was in my ice cream.
‎I almost swallowed my own engagement ring.
‎Apparently, he hid the ring
‎in the ice cream.
‎Do people still propose like that?
‎Are you all right?
‎Yes.
‎After we're done, shall we go for a walk?
‎It's really nice out.
‎-Go for a walk?
‎-Yeah.
‎He asked me out to eat,
‎then suggested we take a walk.
‎The flowers are in full bloom.
‎They are.
‎How pretty.
‎Then he said we should sit on a bench,
‎so I did without a second thought.
‎Suddenly, he got down on one knee
‎and put the ring on my finger.
‎Just a moment, Yeo-ri.
‎Wait, right here and now?
‎I got something on my shoe.
‎On your shoe?
‎There, all done.
‎Your shoe, huh?
‎Your feet must hurt.
‎No, it's fine.
‎Shall we sit down for a bit?
‎Sure.
‎-Here?
‎-Yes.
‎Hold on, Yeo-ri.
‎Cover up with this.
‎Thank you.
‎You won't sit with me?
‎What's wrong?
‎You might find this a bit uncomfortable,
‎but I need to give you something
‎before we get engaged.
‎Like what?
‎Stay right here and rest for a bit.
‎I left it in the car. I won't be long.
‎-Wait here.
‎-Well…
‎Take your time.
‎Gosh, why do you keep
‎getting down on your knee?
‎Yeo-ri.
‎My hand acupuncture needle?
‎How come…
‎Wait a minute. Why is this…
‎-Why--
‎-I'm leaving.
‎Just a minute. Wait…
‎Wait. Stop, Yeo-ri!
‎Yeo-ri, wait. Yeo-ri!
‎Exactly.
‎It just happened to be in a box
‎that looked exactly like a ring box.
‎It was so embarrassing.
‎I wouldn't say I was disappointed.
‎You know, it was just embarrassing
‎for expecting something.
‎The engagement ceremony's coming up,
‎and I guess I'd gotten my hopes up.
‎Is that from a set of matching rings?
‎I see.
‎That's what it's like.
‎How did I mess that up?
‎-"Gang-uk."
‎-Stay still.
‎"You want to marry me?"
‎Hyeong-min, come here
‎and hold his hand still.
‎Are you not allowed to touch her hand?
‎There's a reason for this, okay?
‎Just stay still this time.
‎-Keep still.
‎-You're so gruff.
‎Come on, cooperate.
‎We're almost there.
‎Man, I even practiced
‎until I had it perfect.
‎Seriously…
‎Hello, this is Gang-uk's grandmother.
‎Yes, hello.
‎I hope everything is fine on your end.
‎Yes, thanks to you.
‎It's just that
‎there's some news about Gang-uk.
‎Did something happen to Mr. Ma?
‎Oh, it's not bad news.
‎It's good news, actually.
‎He's met a nice young lady
‎and hopes to get married soon.
‎They'll hold an engagement ceremony first,
‎and the wedding will happen
‎when the time is right.
‎That's great news. Congratulations.
‎Thank you.
‎I owe this all to you
‎and your son, Ji-hwan…
‎I'm so grateful
‎and sorry for everything.
‎Not at all.
‎I'm so happy for you.
‎So what's the young lady like?
‎Oh, well,
‎in some sense,
‎she's too good for him
‎that I can't help but be concerned.
‎But what can I say
‎when Gang-uk insists he's in love?
‎Yes, of course.
‎If he likes her, that's all that matters.
‎If you're free,
‎would you like to come?
‎I'm actually in New York right now,
‎so I have other plans.
‎I see. That won't work out then.
‎I hope your plans go well.
‎Feel free to call me whenever you wish.
‎I will. Congratulations again.
‎Thank you. Goodbye now.
‎The donor's heart has been removed.
‎Grandma?
‎The engagement ceremony date is set.
‎I thought it'd be better
‎to tell you myself
‎than to have you hear it
‎from someone else.
‎I appreciate that,
‎but I can't say I'm happy for you.
‎I was actually confident until now.
‎But for the first time, I have regrets.
‎I should've come back to Korea sooner.
‎Love is all about timing, after all.
‎I guess I missed out…
‎on the first time.
‎"The first time"?
‎You knew I liked you, didn't you?
‎It hurts a lot, actually.
‎But Yeo-ri.
‎I'm not giving up.
‎I'll just have to do things differently
‎from now on.
‎I should go.
‎Min-hwan.
‎You came to see Yeo-ri.
‎You must've heard
‎about the engagement then.
‎Come on.
‎You sounded so confident last time,
‎I thought you had a plan.
‎I'll be in touch.
‎-Ma!
‎-Hey.
‎Do you have lunch plans today?
‎Not exactly.
‎Good. How about we have lunch together?
‎There are people I'd like you to meet.
‎-Sure.
‎-Great.
‎Here.
‎Ma, this group isn't for just anyone.
‎We let you in without a screening
‎because you'll marry into the Reina Group.
‎People love to gossip,
‎saying we just married up.
‎But let's be honest, they're just jealous.
‎Oh, of course.
‎By the way,
‎thanks for your help last time.
‎Not at all.
‎What's this about?
‎My brother-in-law
‎was found guilty of bribery,
‎but he processed his resignation
‎without further penalties.
‎Thanks to you,
‎I saved face with my in-laws.
‎Good. That's great to hear.
‎Park, I'm the one who got
‎that troublemaker brother-in-law
‎an executive job at my wife's company.
‎Of course I'm grateful for that.
‎But I managed to get the case dropped
‎when a subsidiary of your wife's company
‎was charged with breaking the labor laws.
‎-Cheers.
‎-Let's drink.
‎All right.
‎By the way, Ma.
‎Remember that we let you in
‎without a screening, all right?
‎I'm talking about Reina.
‎They're famous for their golf courses.
‎We get to book free rounds
‎whenever we want, right?
‎Free rounds, my ass.
‎If you want to play golf,
‎pay for it out of your own pockets.
‎As for what I heard today,
‎I'll be reporting them directly
‎to the inspector general's office.
‎Man, how I wish I could unhear that.
‎That just ruined my day.
‎He's much more of a jerk than I'd heard.
‎I did some digging,
‎but there wasn't much dirt.
‎And there's too little time
‎to set him up for a trap.
‎The best we can do for now
‎is have him demoted to a regional office.
‎How does that sound?
‎I don't think that would hurt him enough.
‎Thanks anyway.
‎I'll arrange a dinner soon.
‎All right. See you soon.
‎CIVIL SERVANT PERSONNEL FILE
‎Hello, sir.
‎No need to thank me.
‎You're our primary bank.
‎I'd like to pay you a visit soon.
‎Yes, but…
‎I'd like someone else to join us that day.
‎That must be him.
‎Hello, Vice President.
‎Director Gong, what perfect timing.
‎What do you mean by that?
‎You know the CEO of CL Group,
‎Kang Min-hwan, right?
‎My goodness, it's been a while.
‎What brings you here?
‎This is the bank
‎we do most of our business with.
‎I was hoping to see you one day.
‎What a pleasant surprise.
‎How did you figure out
‎I'd taken out a loan
‎from the bank on my Reina shares?
‎That loan matures soon.
‎You can't repay the debt in full, can you?
‎At this rate,
‎the bank will take it all.
‎I'll think of a solution.
‎Why would you do that?
‎Is CL Group interested in Reina Group?
‎If that's not the case,
‎is this something personal
‎that involves CEO Cheon Yeo-ri?
‎I was surprised to hear
‎who she'd chosen to marry.
‎Everyone who's in the know
‎in this industry
‎knows you have feelings for her.
‎Given the current circumstances,
‎I figured she'd choose you
‎even if it were for strategic reasons.
‎I can always create new circumstances.
‎When that time comes,
‎the stake you hold could be of great help.
‎CHAIRWOMAN BAEK GYEONG-JA
‎A share transfer was reported to the FSS.
‎Was it on Director Ok's end? How much?
‎Enough to pose a threat.
‎If they get any more
‎than they already have,
‎the affiliate directors' share
‎could become the deciding vote.
‎What's the matter, ma'am?
‎Call Yeo-ri.
‎Will do, ma'am.
‎Grandma.
‎What happened?
‎Her condition suddenly worsened,
‎so we had her admitted for a check-up.
‎This is already the second time.
‎It means I'm at an age
‎where I can't guarantee my health.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎Let's have the engagement ceremony
‎and then the wedding as soon as possible.
‎That way, I can gift Mr. Ma
‎some company shares.
‎Company shares?
‎That has been done before, right?
‎Yes. Most recently,
‎the chairman of PA Group
‎gifted 200,000 shares
‎to his son-in-law after the wedding.
‎It's just so we're prepared.
‎The FSS received a report
‎of a stock transfer.
‎Considering the timing,
‎they could host a sudden
‎extraordinary shareholders' meeting.
‎It's what they did six years ago.
‎And the agenda…
‎will be a motion for my removal.
‎REINA HOTELS & RESORTS
‎HEIRESS CHEON YEO-RI'S ENGAGEMENT
‎TO PROSECUTOR MA GANG-UK
‎SET TO HAPPEN PRIVATELY AT SIENA HALL
‎12 YEARS AGO
‎-Where are you going?
‎-Huh?
‎I told you.
‎I'm going on a trip with Yeo-ri.
‎Your dad's flying home
‎from his business trip today.
‎Do you have to go?
‎Dad flies home once a week,
‎but this is my first trip with Yeo-ri.
‎Goodness, Yeo-ri is all you talk about.
‎Does she know you're like this?
‎Not yet. I might tell her on this trip.
‎Sons are a lost cause once they grow up.
‎I'll be going. And watch your fingers.
‎Wait, Ji-hwan. Come here.
‎What is it?
‎Where's your pendant?
‎-My pendant?
‎-Yeah.
‎It's right here.
‎What if it falls out of your pocket?
‎I told you to wear it at all times.
‎Turn around.
‎I don't like wearing
‎accessories like this.
‎You know you can't go anywhere
‎without this, don't you?
‎It's your grandmother's orders.
‎She hates it when you make plans
‎to go somewhere.
‎Mom.
‎You know this is ridiculous, right?
‎How can a single pendant
‎keep ghosts away from someone?
‎There are things
‎that even science can't explain.
‎Your grandmother feels better
‎knowing you're wearing this,
‎so be a good grandson and keep it on.
‎For her sake
‎and her prayers for you, okay?
‎But why just me when we're twins?
‎She doesn't make Min-hwan wear this.
‎Am I fated to die young?
‎-How could you say such a thing, Ji-hwan?
‎-That hurt.
‎It's just that she makes
‎such a fuss over me.
‎Ji-hwan.
‎Min-hwan. Let's go.
‎I'll take good care of Ji-hwan.
‎Don't you worry.
‎Okay. Have fun.
‎-See you.
‎-Let's go.
‎Don't worry too much.
‎Bye, Mom.
‎You really think wearing that
‎will keep ghosts away?
‎You have to live. I'll die instead.
‎Yeo-ri!
‎Min-hwan!
‎Kang Min-hwan.
‎-Swap out any soggy ones, okay?
‎-Got it, sir.
‎These can't be eaten if they're soggy.
‎Understood.
‎-Top up the wine a bit more.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Be sure to check for allergies.
‎She has a large farm,
‎and she supplied the strawberries.
‎Please, have a taste.
‎The person is unavailable.
‎You will be redirected to--
‎PLEASE JOIN US FOR THE ENGAGEMENT PARTY
‎OF CHEON YEO-RI AND MA GANG-UK
‎GANG-UK
‎Gang-uk?
‎Sorry, I couldn't answer your call
‎because I kept getting calls from work.
‎Where are you now?
‎I'm heading toward the elevator
‎at the basement parking lot.
‎So you're at the hotel, right?
‎Yes. I just got into the elevator.
‎I'll be up soon.
‎Yeo-ri, are you…
‎CALL ENDED
‎What? What's happening?
‎The person is unavailable.
‎You will be redirected to voicemail--
‎Min-hwan.
‎I came to say something.
‎Right now?
‎Can it wait? I have to go somewhere.
‎I need to tell you now.
‎Six years ago,
‎I came to Korea as soon as
‎I heard about your engagement.
‎I wanted to do whatever I could
‎to change your mind.
‎Don't come closer.
‎-Gi-u.
‎-Stay right there!
‎I didn't think I'd actually become haunted
‎just by holding your hand.
‎I'm sorry.
‎I don't think I can marry you. I'm sorry.
‎But…
‎I couldn't approach you,
‎even seeing how distraught you were.
‎I was almost relieved…
‎because I thought
‎I'd be able to stick around.
‎But was I too late?
‎Once again, this is what it's come to.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎I've liked you for a very long time.
‎I don't want to lose you this time.
‎Min-hwan.
‎I'm sorry.
‎I've never
‎thought of you that way.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎I feel uncomfortable
‎talking about this with you.
‎Just like Cha Gi-u,
‎what if Gang-uk can't make it either?
‎Will you be okay with being alone again?
‎You can hold my hand, Yeo-ri.
‎Damn it.
‎Excuse me?
‎The doors won't open!
‎Just like Cha Gi-u,
‎what if Gang-uk can't make it either?
‎Excuse me? The doors won't open!
‎Stay right there!
‎I didn't think I'd actually become haunted
‎-just by holding your hand.
‎-What if Gang-uk can't make it either?
‎Is anyone there?
‎I'm sorry.
‎I don't think I can marry you. I'm sorry.
‎I won't date her.
‎I won't see Yeo-ri ever again.
‎Don't come closer.
‎Don't come any closer!
‎Are you all right, Yeo-ri?
‎Gang-uk.
‎The elevator stopped all of a sudden.
‎I'm sorry.
‎I thought you wouldn't make it.
‎Why wouldn't I make it
‎when I've been waiting for this day?
‎Before we go inside…
‎I wasn't sure what you'd like,
‎so I picked something out myself.
‎What do you think?
‎I was so scared.
‎I wondered if it were the ghosts,
‎or if I was afraid
‎of yet another failed engagement.
‎I guess it was neither.
‎I was just afraid you wouldn't come.
‎That I would…
‎never get to see you again.
‎That's what I was afraid of.
‎Why wouldn't you see me again?
‎I told you
‎that I'll be by your side,
‎wherever you are.
‎I think
‎I really want to…
‎get engaged to you.
‎Will you
‎be my fiancé?
‎SPOOKY IN LOVE
‎Siena Hall's at the center of attention
‎since Yeo-ri's engagement.
‎An extraordinary shareholders' meeting
‎will be held at Reina soon.
‎Is it a serious situation?
‎The dismissal of Cheon Yeo-ri,
‎CEO of Reina Hotel.
‎Ok Gye-hui knows no fear.
‎When will they start?
‎Right away.
‎-Do give us your full support.
‎-Gosh.
‎Are there any shareholders
‎worth contacting?
‎-You'll do it yourself, ma'am?
‎-I have to.
‎Tell me what you need.
‎I'll help with anything.
‎-No way. I won't do it.
‎-Come on.
‎I'm going abroad on a business trip.
‎Yeo-ri must feel cornered
‎to resort to something this ridiculous.
‎It may seem reckless,
‎but I might try something different.
‎Is Kang Min-hwan going too?
‎I think I should come with you.
‎Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim